Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
=Episode 11=
=الحلقة 11=
Ms. Gu.
السيدة جو.
If GL could work with Xinyi,
إذا كان بإمكان GL العمل مع Xinyi،
it would set a new standard for the jewelry industry.
من شأنه أن يضع معيارًا جديدًا لصناعة المجوهرات.
We'd surely be the industry's number one.
من المؤكد أننا سنكون الرقم واحد في الصناعة.
Mr. Lin, fame draws trouble.
السيد لين، الشهرة تجلب المتاعب.
Isn't it better to let all succeed?
أليس من الأفضل أن نترك الجميع ينجحون؟
Xuan, fetch my wine from the car.
شوان، أحضر لي النبيذ من السيارة.
Tonight, I'll have a good drink with the two bosses.
سأتناول مشروبًا جيدًا مع الزعيمين الليلة.
Good idea.
فكرة جيدة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Go.
يذهب.
(Today's dinner guests are ill-intentioned. Backup.)
(ضيوف العشاء اليوم لديهم نوايا سيئة. نسخة احتياطية.)
Something came up. I have to go.
لقد حدث شيء ما. يجب أن أذهب.
Where to?
إلى أين؟
And you said you didn't like her.
وقلت أنك لا تحبها.
Isn't GL backed by Lu Jianhua?
أليس GL مدعومًا من قبل Lu Jianhua؟
If you want a man,
إذا كنت تريد رجلا،
you could just choose me.
يمكنك اختيارني فقط.
I can do that.
انا قادر على فعل ذلك.
My overseas assets are no less than Lu Jianhua's.
أصولي في الخارج لا تقل عن أصول لو جيانهوا.
A woman's destiny
مصير المرأة
is to find a man in the end.
هو العثور على رجل في النهاية.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
A toast to you.
نخب لك.
You speak so pleasantly.
أنت تتحدث بشكل لطيف للغاية.
That's more like it.
هذا أشبه بذلك.
Good.
جيد.
You're really profiting from today's medical fee.
أنت تستفيد حقًا من رسوم الرعاية الطبية اليوم.
You little vixen.
أيها الثعلبة الصغيرة.
What nonsense is this?
ما هذا الهراء؟
- Mr. Lin.
- السيد لين.
Now we're both fighting.
الآن نحن الاثنان نتقاتل.
Your medical fee's gone again.
لقد ذهبت رسومك الطبية مرة أخرى.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
Call the police!
اتصل بالشرطة!
- Calm down. - Call the police!
- اهدأ. - اتصل بالشرطة!
- Lin Xiang!
- لين شيانغ!
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Call the police!
اتصل بالشرطة!
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
You're bleeding?
هل أنت تنزف؟
Call the police.
اتصل بالشرطة.
Alright, I'll go now.
حسنًا، سأذهب الآن.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
هل انت بخير؟ هل انت مصاب؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
Don't look so glum. It's just wine.
لا تبدو كئيبًا جدًا، إنه مجرد نبيذ.
I already know
انا اعرف بالفعل
(Police) what happened.
(الشرطة) ماذا حدث.
This does count as excessive defense.
يعتبر هذا بمثابة دفاع مفرط.
The other party will get a medical appraisal.
سيحصل الطرف الآخر على تقييم طبي.
He insists on legal action.
ويصر على اتخاذ إجراء قانوني.
You weren't even invited to this dinner,
لم تتم دعوتك حتى إلى هذا العشاء،
yet you showed up and attacked someone.
ومع ذلك ظهرت وهاجمت شخصًا ما.
You think you're innocent?
هل تعتقد أنك بريء؟
Even if she's your girlfriend, it's no excuse. Understand?
حتى لو كانت حبيبتك، هذا ليس عذرًا. هل فهمت؟
I...
أنا...
She's not my girlfriend.
إنها ليست صديقتي.
Not your girlfriend?
ليست صديقتك؟
What are you doing then? Acting righteous?
ماذا تفعل إذن؟ هل تتصرف بشكل صحيح؟
I'm her boss.
أنا رئيسها.
I get how you feel,
أنا أفهم ما تشعر به،
but hitting people is wrong.
لكن ضرب الناس خطأ.
Understand?
يفهم؟
That brat dares to hit me!
هذا الوغد يجرؤ على ضربي!
You old pervert!
أيها المنحرف العجوز!
You lecher, how dare you act so righteous?
أيها الفاسق، كيف تجرؤ على التصرف بهذه الطريقة الصالحة؟
Wait and see!
انتظر وشاهد!
Brat!
شقي!
You'll get a criminal record, you know that?
سوف تحصل على سجل جنائي، هل تعلم ذلك؟
You might as well go and talk it out.
قد يكون من الأفضل أن تذهب وتتحدث في الأمر.
Apologize or offer compensation if needed.
اعتذر أو قدم تعويضًا إذا لزم الأمر.
He harassed her. Why should we apologize?
لقد تحرش بها. لماذا نعتذر؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Officer.
ضابط.
I'll go apologize.
سأذهب للاعتذار.
Apologize?
يعتذر؟
Why should we apologize?
لماذا يجب علينا الإعتذار؟
Lu Xingchen, let go.
لو شينغتشن، اتركه.
Let go!
اتركه!
Sir.
سيد.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Alright, Sir.
حسنا سيدي.
Don't be mad.
لا تغضب.
Officer.
ضابط.
May I speak privately with Mr. Lin?
هل يمكنني التحدث مع السيد لين على انفراد؟
You may.
يمكنك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Watch your attitude.
راقب موقفك.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
I'm sorry for what happened.
أنا آسف لما حدث.
I apologize to you.
أعتذر لك.
As long as you agree to one condition,
طالما أنك توافق على شرط واحد،
I can settle this with you.
أستطيع تسوية هذا الأمر معك.
You're negotiating with me?
هل تتفاوض معي؟
Do you think you have the right to bargain with me?
هل تعتقد أن لديك الحق في المساومة معي؟
Mr. Jing's half of the jewelry went to Xinyi, right?
نصف مجوهرات السيد جينغ ذهبت إلى شينيي، أليس كذلك؟
And about Xinyi's slander against GL earlier,
وأما بخصوص افتراءات شينيي ضد GL في وقت سابق،
I can give you the original contract.
أستطيع أن أعطيك العقد الأصلي.
I wonder if you're satisfied with this gift.
أتساءل إذا كنت راضيا عن هذه الهدية.
What's the condition?
ما هي الحالة؟
Sign a letter of forgiveness for Lu Xingchen.
توقيع خطاب الغفران للو شينغتشين.
I can sign it,
يمكنني التوقيع عليه
but I can't swallow this anger.
ولكنني لا أستطيع التغلب على هذا الغضب.
Ms. Gu, slap yourself three times,
السيدة جو، صفعي نفسك ثلاث مرات،
then I can forgive him.
حينها أستطيع أن أسامحه.
Isn't it just to cheer Mr. Lin up?
أليس هذا فقط من أجل تحسين مزاج السيد لين؟
Easy.
سهل.
Gu Liusu, what are you doing?
جو ليوسو، ماذا تفعل؟
Lin Xiang, are you looking for trouble?
لين شيانغ، هل تبحث عن المتاعب؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What are you doing? Mind your attitude!
ماذا تفعل؟ انتبه لسلوكك!
Lu Xingchen, this is a police station.
لو شينغتشين، هذا مركز للشرطة.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Officer.
ضابط.
He keeps giving you trouble. How can I stay calm?
إنه يسبب لك المشاكل باستمرار. كيف يمكنني أن أبقى هادئًا؟
Mr. Lu.
السيد صن
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Be careful with your behavior in public.
كن حذرا في سلوكك في الأماكن العامة.
Don't cause more trouble.
لا تسبب المزيد من المتاعب.
Officer.
ضابط.
Sorry for the trouble.
عذرا على الإزعاج.
It's the kid's fault.
إنه خطأ الطفل.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Sign here.
التوقيع هنا.
Mr. Lu, I'll go now.
السيد لو سأذهب الآن.
Get in the car.
ادخل إلى السيارة.
You said you'd handle Lin Xiang
لقد قلت أنك ستتعامل مع لين شيانغ
and look after Gu Liusu.
والعناية بـ Gu Liusu.
Is this how you do it?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تفعل بها ذلك؟
Should I beat someone and end up in the police station,
هل يجب أن أضرب شخصًا وينتهي بي الأمر في مركز الشرطة،
then have your father clean up your mess?
ثم اطلب من والدك أن ينظف الفوضى التي خلفتها؟
Get in the car.
ادخل إلى السيارة.
Still not getting in?
هل لا تزال غير قادر على الدخول؟
I'm taking Gu Liusu home.
سأخذ Gu Liusu إلى المنزل.
I told you to watch my son.
لقد قلت لك أن تراقب ابني.
Is this how you do it?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تفعل بها ذلك؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
How about a walk?
ماذا عن المشي؟
Okay.
تمام.
I was impulsive today. I didn't expect you'd come.
كنتُ متهورًا اليوم. لم أتوقع مجيئك.
I was worried about you.
لقد كنت قلقا عليك.
I just wanted to use the contract to vent my anger,
أردت فقط استخدام العقد للتنفيس عن غضبي،
but dragged you into it.
لكن جرّك إليه.
It's nothing like that.
إنه ليس مثل ذلك على الإطلاق.
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
Next time, don't drink so much.
في المرة القادمة، لا تشرب كثيرا.
They won't respect you more
لن يحترمونك أكثر
just because you drink more.
فقط لأنك تشرب أكثر.
You don't need to prove your worth to anyone.
لا تحتاج إلى إثبات قيمتك لأي شخص.
You're already strong enough.
أنت قوية بما فيه الكفاية بالفعل.
♪I never knew it could be so easy♪
♪لم أكن أعلم أنه يمكن أن يكون الأمر بهذه السهولة♪
♪I never thought it could be so true♪
♪لم أكن أتصور أبدًا أن هذا قد يكون صحيحًا إلى هذا الحد♪
♪But every time I close my eyes♪
♪ولكن في كل مرة أغمض عيني♪
♪I feel a peace in me arise♪
♪أشعر بالسلام في داخلي♪
♪I never knew love could be so healing♪
♪لم أكن أعلم أن الحب يمكن أن يكون شافيًا إلى هذا الحد♪
♪I never thought I could learn to feel♪
♪لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أنني سأتمكن من تعلم الشعور♪
♪But when we're standin' side by side♪
♪ولكن عندما نقف جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪Well, there's no darkness left to hide♪
♪حسنًا، لم يعد هناك ظلام ليختبئ♪
Let me send you home.
دعني أرسلك إلى المنزل.
♪Fallen so fast. For you, right into your arms♪
♪سقطتُ بسرعة. لأجلك، بين ذراعيك♪
♪And I, I just wanna love you well with all that I am♪
♪وأنا، أريد فقط أن أحبك بكل ما أوتيت من قوة♪
♪So I give you my heart♪
♪لذا أعطيك قلبي♪
I'm home. You should head back.
أنا في المنزل. يجب عليك العودة.
You still need to report to Mr. Lu.
لا يزال يتعين عليك إبلاغ السيد لو.
♪No words could ever do it justice♪
♪لا توجد كلمات يمكنها أن تصف الأمر على الإطلاق♪
Aren't you inviting me in to sit awhile?
ألا تدعوني للجلوس لفترة؟
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
♪But I can't escape♪
♪لكنني لا أستطيع الهروب♪
♪The memories of you♪
♪ذكرياتك♪
♪The harder I try to forget♪
♪كلما حاولت أن أنسى♪
♪The more you come back to me♪
♪كلما عدت إلي أكثر♪
♪Two hearts once in love collide and shatter into pieces♪
♪قلبان كانا في حالة حب تصادما وتحطما إلى قطع♪
♪How can I piece myself together again?♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أجمع نفسي مرة أخرى؟♪
♪Funny, isn't it?♪
♪مضحك، أليس كذلك؟♪
♪Only after losing you did I see your love was worth keeping♪
♪فقط بعد أن فقدتك رأيت أن حبك يستحق الاحتفاظ به♪
♪I hate myself for not being brave, for not trying♪
♪أكره نفسي لعدم كوني شجاعًا، لعدم محاولتي♪
♪For letting you slip away into the crowd with my own hands♪
♪لأني سمحت لك بالانزلاق إلى الحشد بيدي ♪
♪Guess we just met at the wrong time♪
♪أعتقد أننا التقينا في الوقت الخطأ♪
♪What's left of our love is nothing but ashes♪
♪ما تبقى من حبنا ليس سوى رماد♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪At the wrong time, I found the one I loved most♪
♪في الوقت الخطأ، وجدت الشخص الذي أحببته أكثر♪
♪Does that still count as luck?♪
♪هل لا يزال هذا يعتبر حظًا؟♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪